## Isha Dabas

I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, self-taught developer and designer with over 3 years of experience in Web development and Graphic designing. I am able to work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative. I am able to work well under pressure and adhere to strict deadlines. I am always keen on learning something new or improving by working on personal projects or reading blogs.

**EXPERIENCE** 

## Digisoft IT Solutions Pvt Ltd - Full Stack Developer

May 2022 - August 2022

- Micro-services based architecture.
- Implemented controllers and wrote tests for various microservices.
- Developing a frontend website for the same in **Next.js**.

## Digisoft IT Solutions Pvt Ltd -Full Stack Developer

March 2023 - Present

- Developed E-Commerce Website for Indian Food and Groceries.
- Developed product API for the website in ExpressJS and MongoDB.
- Testing and Debugging the code.

## **EDUCATION**

Bennett University, Greater Noida — Bachelor's in Computer Applications (BCA)

October 2020 - June 2023

Lancer's Convent Sr. Sec. School, New Delhi — *High School*March 2006 - March 2020

#### **PROJECTS**

<u>Assets-Management-System(AsMS)</u> — (Full Stack{Next.js, Node.js and Amazon S3})

July 2022 - November 2022

- Developed a responsive react app in Next with beautiful UI designed with
   Chakra
- Stores assets on **S3** and interacts with the app using **MongoDB**.
- Visualized cards for Assets in particular categories.
- Last but not the least in app assets(pdf) viewer(React Library).

Portfolio: Portfolio Website

Email: ishadabas26001@gmail.com

ishadabas@icloud.com **Github:** @IshaDabas **LinkedIn:** @isha-dabas **Medium:** @ishadabas

Phone Number: (+91) 9599137351

#### **SKILLS**

- > React JS
- Next.js
- ➤ Node.js
- > Typescript
- > Javascript
- Cyber Security
- > Ethical Hacking
- Adobe XD
- > Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- ➤ UI/UX
- ➤ Firebase
- > SQL
- ➤ MongoDB
- > AWS cloud service

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

Node|S-Coding Blocks

Cyber security essentials

**HTML Tags and Attributes** 

<u>PHP</u>

Fortinet Information Security
Awareness Certificate

ECC Web Application Hacking and Security

**ECC Certified Ethical Hacker** 

**AWS Cloud Foundations** 

<u>Infosys Explore Machine Learning Using</u>
Python

Microsoft Azure Certified {2} (AZ-900 & DP-900)

# <u>NextFlix(Netflix-clone</u>) — Full Stack{React.js and Firebase}) May 2022 - July 2022

- Developed a responsive react app like Netflix.
- Multiple profiles and authentication are implemented on firebase.
- Data fetched from APIs and user data stored in the **firestore database**.
- Payment is handled by the **STRIPE** payments gateway.

## Portfolio-Website — (Front End{React.js})

- Created a personal portfolio website using **React.js**.
- Implemented about, blogs, memories and projects showcase all using aesthetically designed **Custom CSS(Tailwind)**.

#### **CLUBS AND ORGANIZATIONS**

Coding Blocks

Campus Ambassador | September 2022 - May 2023

**Anime Club** 

**Event Manager | May 2021 - May 2022** 

**Anime Club** 

Social Media Head | November 2022 - May 2023

**BU Gamers** 

Event Manager and Core Team Member | May 2021 - May 2022

### **LANGUAGES**

- ENGLISH (Fluent)
- HINDI (Native)

### **EXTRA-CURRICULAR**

- Basketball Team (Inter University)
- Pc Gamer (Esports and Casual)
- Gym and Athletics
- Sketching and Illustrations